Samia Matin

AL, USA | (334) 663-1842

m.samia.au@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/samiamtn/

Summary

Software Developer with 7+ years of experience in coding, quality assurance testing, web, game, and app development, reviewing program functionality, establishing system improvements, and testing for security precautions. Highly adept at developing software for desktop computers, cloud integrations, and mobile devices.

Skills

→ JavaScript
→ Java
→ Postman
→ SQL
→ React
→ Heroku
→ C++
→ Backend
→ C/C#
→ Nodejs
→ Frontend

> .NET > VS Code/Eclipse

Work Experience

SDET

Global Tell Link, Remote, May 2018-Jan 2022

- Created testing systems to identify issues within software.
- Evaluated existing technology to identify areas of improvement.
- Built test automation framework for various software projects.

Selenium Trainee Intern, July 2021-Dec 2021

White Circle Schools, Remote

• Trained by a professional in QA Testing software with Java, C#, and with Maven.

Junior App Developer

Digital Punk Studios, Remote, Aug 2014-May 2018

• Collaborated with a team of 4 other engineers to design, engineer, and deploy an Android application with JavaScript, HTML5, and CSS3 for Digital Punk Studios.

Education

Bachelor's of Computer Science Saint Leo University WorldWide - Jan 2019-Mar 2021 Web Development Specialization CareerFoundry - Sept 2022-Present

Certifications, Awards, Honors

Web Development, freeCodeCamp - July 2022 Google Data Analytics, Coursera - November 2022 Dean's List, Saint Leo University - Fall 2020 Omega Nu Lambda, Saint Leo University - Spring 2021